<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog-rsses on mysticTot</title>
    <link>https://mysticTot.github.io/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog-rsses on mysticTot</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 20:09:23 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mysticTot.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>ILUG-D Again and Forever</title>
      <link>https://mystictot.github.io/blog/ILUG-D-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 20:09:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mystictot.github.io/blog/ILUG-D-meetup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Being an FOSS enthusiast, I always wanted to meet old and experineced guys who have been  using linux and other open source technlogies from many years.
I heard there use to be an India Linux User Group Delhi aka ILUGD and it was one of the most prominent LUG of India. But it was totally inactive ever since Mr Raj Mathur has passed away. It was a  shock to the community that led no ILUG-D meeting from then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been using linux for more than 2 years and with time my interest in linux has become a passion,
specially in linux kernel. So, I want to be a part of linux community of Delhi-NCR and I found that there is no active community in Delhi-NCR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I started talking people about this, I noticed that many new people(including me) and old folks want a community rather want to revive the old ILUGD.
Once we started to have words about LUG, many people turned up and started taking it. One of my friend, Sahil aka warlord77 took a very good initiative by started conversation with old ILUGD folks like Satyakaam, Gora Mohanty, Prof Andrew and Prof Sanjeev, Aakshay, Anuvrat and many others.
With that spark, we get a second and most important chance in &lt;a href=&#34;https://in.pycon.org/2016/&#34;&gt;Pycon India 2016&lt;/a&gt; to have words about ILUGD with old folks and and finally after having a good discussion we decided to have a IlUGD meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I initiated the mail for venue, i learned my first lesson about  DO&amp;rsquo;s and Don&amp;rsquo;ts of mailing list.
With only 2 days, left we were not sure about the venue and we were planning the meetup. But with 2 days remaining we received invitation for the venue and that was more than enough from the folks. We finalised &lt;a href=&#34;http://efy.in/&#34;&gt;Efy&lt;/a&gt;( Special Thanks to Rahul Chopra and Neeraj Sahay) as our venue for the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was good to see a huge support be it on &lt;a href=&#34;http://frodo.hserus.net/mailman/listinfo/ilugd&#34;&gt;mailing list&lt;/a&gt;, Telegram group and &lt;code&gt;#linux-india&lt;/code&gt; irc channel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all rush and hush we finally managed to organise ILUG-D meeting.
Here is the photo of meeting
&lt;img src=&#34;https://mysticTot.github.io/static/photo_2016-10-16_22-32-59.png?raw=true&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had a good very good discussion.
We have a long way to go but an initiative has already been taken to have LUG meetings and for that  credits go to all those folks who have given us both direct and indirect support be it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;Motivation,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;Guidaince,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;Venue sponsorship,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;Suggestion,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;Participation,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ndash;Critics and feedback,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And Everything that let this meeting happened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope  more participation in our next meeting which is going happen on 5th November, 2016 because it is the community who makes Open Source successful.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>